[{"answer": "Wow! The place looks great. Really great", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "\"Lik", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What do you mean? It's comfortable. For T.V. I love that chair", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "It goes with me", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "The one you always slip into it when you get nervous.", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Admit it. You liked me. You were interested", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "That's what I keep asking myself", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I've been checking", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What about the sweater you knitted that was too big", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Four sizes", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Four sizes", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You couldn't throw it out. He saw. He was there. This is for real. Hey do you hear me up there", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "How should I know? It's not like I can see him. I just hear his voice", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He says he's holding your hand", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "This is sick. This is really sick. How can you swallow this crap? Who knows if this guy exists? Maybe she's just setting someone up", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Find out? What are you talking about", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "This isn't possible. There were words, private things. How could she have known all that", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Ways? What ways", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "It's your mind, you idiot. It's all in the mind. The problem is you think you're still real, that you're standin' on the floor, that you're wearin' those clothes. Bullshit! You don't even have a body anymore. It's all up here. You wanna move things, you gotta use your mind. You gotta focus! You hear what I'm saying", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't know how you focus! You just focus", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "How long have you been here", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Someone pushed you", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Since they pushed me", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah, someone pushed me", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I need your help, my friend. There's something we need to do", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Give it up? I'm already dead", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Forget it. I'm not doin' anything. You're holdin' on to a life that don't want you no more. Give it up", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Dead, yeah, but you ain't finished dyin'. Give up the ghost", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Hello. my friend speaking", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Mr. my frien", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No. I'm here for the fun of it", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Tell him my friend's here", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "A long time", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "How are my friend and my friend doin'", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " Why, they're just fine, thank you. Nice of you to ask. And how is your... family", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Well, isn't that wonderful", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Good old my friend. Got a real head on his shoulders", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "\"He", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " Then my mother took all the money from the oil wells and put it in gasoline pumps. Every gas station has 'em you know, sometimes six or more. It adds up", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " Well, I've got to leave. It's been a pleasure doin' business with you. Say", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "my friend? What happened", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Dead!  Oh, thank God. It's over", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "my friend? Is that you", "docId": "Ghost.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I hear you, my friend", "qsentId": 44}]